There are so many people here.
It's hard to keep up with them.
The members are getting closer.
They're stretching.
They're all cute, but they're on my right leg.
What?
No, no, no.
The members are getting closer.
Zudon!
We're on YouTube now.
Yay!
Where are we?
Let's go.
We're at Harajuku Station.
It's hard to keep up with them.
We've never been to Harajuku.
Oh, right.
We've always wanted to go to a shiny place called Harajuku.
We've always wanted to go to Harajuku.
This is our first time in Harajuku.
We got 10,000 yen here.
How do you feel?
It's crazy.
Harajuku looks like a monument.
A monument?
A chaku.
Let's go into Takeshita Street.
Is it pink?
Wow, there are so many people.
Can we go in?
What should we eat first?
Sorry, I'm talking about what we should eat.
Where do you want to go?
We haven't eaten anything since this morning.
I've been holding it in.
We're all ready.
There's a store that I really want to go to.
I want to get a ticket for it.
I got it.
What's the name of the store?
Harajuku Frying Potatoes.
No, it's not.
It's not Frying Potatoes.
Wait, it's 1 o'clock.
I can't go today.
I'm sorry.
I was really happy to hear that I could shoot a video with you.
I'm happy.
We've been talking a lot lately.
I've been thinking that you're a hundred times more interesting than I thought.
It's my line.
That's why I said it was fun to come with you.
I'm happy.
When I first met Moeka.
We met face to face.
Rainbow?
Wait.
Let's talk about it.
Let's talk about Moeka.
It's like a dream.
It's rainbow.
It's like Harajuku.
Isn't this a famous one?
This is a long one.
What Mirine is attracted to now is the 10-yen rainbow version.
Which one do you want?
Rainbow.
Sand.
Rainbow Sand.
Let's go buy it.
I have to get permission.
Excuse me.
We're at Nogizaka 46.
I'd like to buy something at this store.
I'd like to use it for YouTube.
Is it okay if I show you?
Don't show my face.
It's okay.
Thank you very much.
Mirine is waiting for 7 minutes for the rainbow sand.
I want to buy the longest potato in Japan.
I've been watching this on YouTube for a long time.
I wanted to eat it.
I've been longing for it.
I'd like to buy it now.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
I've got permission.
I'd like to line up and eat it.
I'm going to film with Mirine this time.
I was just saying that I was really happy.
Mirine is so natural.
It's really fun to go together.
I can talk to her without filters.
I can't express my feelings to her directly.
I like Mirine very much.
I won't say it to her.
I got it.
I feel like I'm being taken by Mirine.
Here comes Yada with a long potato.
It's Yada with a long potato.
It's me.
It's Rainbow Mirine.
Rainbow Mirine.
If I don't stretch it quickly, I might not be able to eat cheese.
I've been wanting to eat this for a long time.
I'm going.
Please.
Will it stretch?
I can see it.
It's stretching.
Pink and yellow are strong.
I'm going to eat it.
Please.
I'm glad.
Cheese?
There's garlic in the cheese.
Garlic looks like this.
It's delicious because there are too many gaps.
Can I have a bite?
Since you love cheese so much.
It's delicious.
It's garlic.
It's garlic compared to this.
Is it delicious?
When Gatcha Gatcha was in my hometown,
I've only seen two or three of them next to the supermarket.
I wanted to go to a place full of Gatcha Gatcha.
I'm here.
We came to this capsule lab.
Let's go in.
What do you want?
Do you want to see food?
The anime is over there.
I did it.
There's one here too.
There's Kirarin's Voyation.
I miss it.
It's my youth.
What should I do?
There's Death Note.
I'm going to eat it.
There's Captain Sakura.
There's Death Note.
There's a school address.
Death Note is good, but wait a minute.
There's Death Note.
Calm down.
Listen to me.
I just saw Death Note the other day.
Death Note is very hot right now.
I'm going to play Death Note.
I'm happy no matter what comes out.
What's the level?
It's L.
Isn't it 2?
It's 2.
I'm going up.
I'm going to play it next.
I lost my bangs clip recently.
Ah! Understood.
It's cute no matter what, but I'm going to play the one that came out.
What will come out?
It's cute. It looks like a spaceship.
It's cute.
Is it like this?
I'm going to play the next one.
I'm going to play this one.
It's a oyster.
It's a fluffy-looking oyster.
I'm going to play a fluffy-looking oyster.
What's your goal?
It's cute. The name is cute.
It's a hit oyster.
Is it okay to call it a hit oyster?
Is it a hit?
My goal is a big oyster.
It's a big oyster.
It's big.
It's the center of the oyster's single.
It's a big oyster.
Come out.
What?
Is it a hit?
It's a hit, isn't it?
Don't say it.
Yes.
It's a hit oyster.
It's a hit.
Is it okay?
I'm worried about eating the next oyster.
From now on, I'm going to Nengan.
I'm going to Nengan.
Going towards the shaved ice of Tokyo.
I haven't eaten yet the fluffy-looking shaved ice in Tokyo.
I'm going to eat that.
We talked about where to go last night.
I want to go there with you two.
I'm looking forward to it.
I found it.
What should we do?
Let's eat one by one.
Let's go home.
I've already decided.
There is only one option.
I've been looking into it for a long time.
I've already decided.
Let's go together.
It's the same.
Let's eat the same food.
Let's eat.
It's amazing.
It's like an analysis.
An analysis?
What does an analysis mean?
I'm sorry.
I don't have the ability to speak.
An analysis is...
An analysis?
An analysis of food.
An analysis of people on the other side of food.
It's too mysterious.
Isn't this amazing?
Is this what an analysis is?
It's like an interview.
An analysis?
I've never done an analysis.
Me neither.
What?
What are you talking about?
You were going to say that.
Yes.
At first,
I was going to say that I hate it.
I'm going to say that.
That's not an analysis.
I hate it.
Well...
An analysis?
You're getting along, right?
When we first met,
I thought you were definitely a half.
I thought you were a half.
We went to buy lunch together for the first time.
You bought a burrito.
You bought a burrito, and I thought you were a half.
That's too mysterious.
I like burritos, but it looks like it's half.
She has a beautiful face, so I thought it would be half.
I talked to her in simple words.
Say hello.
It was awkward at first.
I was surprised when I talked to her.
She said, that's right.
I wondered why she had such a face.
I thought I could talk.
I thought it was a high-spec half.
No, it was Jun Japan.
At Miyagi Park the other day,
when Mirine was taking pictures,
Ikeda-san was in the picture.
I was a little jealous.
I was shooting a video.
She came to me, but I didn't have a battery on the phone.
I couldn't save the video.
It's so sad.
I couldn't believe it.
He said he didn't have it on his phone.
I was told by Hina that I am like Kubo.
I'm sorry, Kubo-san.
But there are words like that.
It's like a YouTuber.
We went to Yamada Combi.
Mirine gave us a name.
If you have anything you want us to do at Yamada Combi,
please write it in the comments.
It's a really good name.
I like it recently.
When I first heard it,
I thought it was an idol name.
What is it?
There's nothing.
What is it? I'm curious. Tell me.
I just thought of it.
Can you use this?
There's this nickname.
Nickname?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No?
It's really cute.
When I said I wanted an nickname,
there was a nickname I thought of.
He thought of it for me.
It's really cute.
Here we go.
It's Moechakka Fire.
What do you think?
What do you think of Moechakka Fire?
It's ready.
Moechakka Fire is here.
It's here.
We've arrived.
It looks good.
Look.
There's ice cream, cheesecake, and mango on it.
It's so special.
Let's eat.
Really?
It's dripped on your foot.
It's dripping.
It's good.
Can you do something new?
It's dripping.
No, you can't.
Wait a minute.
The ice cream is too shocking.
I can't eat it.
Is it milk?
Oh, no.
What?
Is it snow?
Is it over there?
It's fluffy.
I break the ice cream with my hands at home.
I often eat it like shaved ice.
It's completely different.
I've never heard of such a person.
It's going to be gone soon.
It's more like a curry drink.
It's amazing.
When I eat it, there's a lot of mango sauce in it.
I'm not tired of it.
I think shaved ice is often made at festivals because there is not enough syrup at the end.
This is shaved ice that doesn't need such worries.
Perfect mango.
It's delicious.
I'll eat mango and cheesecake together.
Is it okay?
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Is it okay?
Thank you for the meal.
What did you say again?
We've finished eating.
We don't sync, do we?
This is the end of our first trip to Harajuku.
Moechaka Fire, how did it go?
Moechaka Fire was the first time she had a solo shoot with Mirine.
I was very happy to have a solo shoot with two people.
I was happy to have Mirine.
I'd like to go out again together.
Let's go! Wherever you want.
What about Mirine?
Mirine too, how do I say it?
With Yada, Fire, together - Only Yada is fine
I am happy that she has come, that we finally went together in Harajuku
I was very funny, I am very happy.
Like high school girls?
Yes, like JK.
It was fun.
Please come to Harajuku.
Please come.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching!